https://usflag.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

US Flag and Flagpole Supply, Inc.
usflag@usflag.com
US Flag and Flagpole Supply, Inc.
Menu
US & State FlagsOutdoor FlagsU.S. FlagsNylonPolyesterTexas FlagsNylonPolyesterState FlagsNylonPolyesterIndoor FlagsU.S. FlagsState FlagsHistoricalBetsy RossBenningtonGadsdenStar Spangled BannerMilitary FlagsMemorialMemorialSupportSupport Our TroopsMilitary BranchesAir ForceArmyCoast GuardMarine CorpsNavyOther FlagsFlag SetsUSA Flag SetsState Flag SetsArmed Forces Flag SetsInternational Flag SetsReligious Flag SetsInternationalIndoor FlagsOceania FlagsSouth American FlagsNorth American FlagsEuropean FlagsAsian FlagsAfrican FlagsOutdoor FlagsOceania FlagsSouth American FlagsNorth American FlagsEuropean FlagsAsian FlagsAfrican FlagsReligiousChristian FlagsCatholic (Papal) FlagsIsrael FlagsEpiscopal FlagsCustom
Custom Flags
Custom flags and banners are the perfect way to present your company professionally, grab attention of passers by at trade shows, advertise your new product, welcome a traveling friend of family member home, celebrate a happy event, and much more.
Place your custom flag request conveniently online and one of our customer service representatives will contact you to collect your logo, color and application needs.
Begin a custom project here
Prepare Your Files
All files must be vector, and fonts used within the file should be converted to outlines to avoid font substitution from occurring.
Read more
Begin a Project
Visit our custom flag quote request page by clicking the link bellow, fill out the form and send off your request.
Read more
Enjoy your Custom Flag
After you've received and accepted our response to your quote request, you'll work for awhile with our team to create your custom flag. Then you'll have nothing to do but enjoy the first fight.
FlagpolesCommercialAluminum PolesExternal CleatInternal Cam CleatInternal WinchFiberglass PolesExternal CleatInternal Cam CleatInternal WinchResidentialAluminum PolesExternal CleatFiberglass PolesExternal CleatAccessoriesFinial OrnamentsFlash CollarsCleatsTruck AssembliesHalyard (Rope)CounterweightsBeaded Retainer RingsSnaphooks and ConnectorsMonster Flagpoles
Monster Flagpoles
U.S. Flag & Flagpole Supply is the World’s leading expert in the design, manufacture, integration, and installation of record-breaking Steel Monster Flagpoles.
With over 60 years of combined experience, U.S. Flag & Flagpole Supply has manufactured and installed more flagpoles 100'-410' around the globe than any other company.
We are the source when it comes to flagpoles of this magnitude.
This privacy policy sets out how US Flag and Flagpole Supply, Inc uses and protects any information
that you give US Flag and Flagpole Supply, Inc when you use this website.
US Flag and Flagpole Supply, Inc is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website,
then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
US Flag and Flagpole Supply, Inc may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.
You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we
think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website
according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure,
we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure
the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic
and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical
analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful
and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links
to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst
visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate
that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes,
you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at
usflag@usflagpole.onmicrosoft.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission
or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information
about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to
.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete,
please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address.
We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE name
COOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
© Copyrighted by US Flag & Flag Supply, LLC. All right reserved. Web site design & development: Tigren E-commerce Co. LTD.
